Guide to the Rick Lazio Papers, 1981–2005
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series II. Congressional Papers
  - Event
    - Harvard University – Institute of Politics, (Itinerary, Correspondence), 11 Dec 2000 (Box 60)
    - House G.O.P. Retreat, Nemocolin Woodlands Conference Center, (Itinerary, Correspondence), 3-5 Feb 2000 (Box 60)
    - House – Senate Dinner, (Talking Points, Correspondence), 24 May 2000 (Box 60)
    - Ithaca Republican Committee Lincoln Day Dinner, (Itinerary, Correspondence), 12 Feb 2000 (Box 60)
    - J.F.K. School Of Government/Bipartisan Congressional Health Policy Conference, (Itinerary, Conference Notes), 20-22 Jan 2000 (Box 60)
    - John Chafee Dinner, (Speech Text, Program From Event), 9 May 2000 (Box 60)
    - Lincoln Club of Northern California, (Itinerary, Correspondence), 24-26 Apr 2000 (Box 60)
    - List Net Microsoft Announcement, (Press Release, Remarks By R. Lazio), Feb 2000 (Box 60)
    - Speaking Engagement Invitations, (Correspondence, Memoranda), Jan 2000 (Box 60)
    - Speaking Engagement Invitations, (Correspondence, Memoranda), Feb 2000 (Box 60)
    - Speaking Engagement Invitations, (Correspondence…Includes Invitation From Fidney Cancer Association Honoring Rick Lazio 3/27/2000), Mar 2000; (2 folders) (Box 61)
    - Speaking Engagement Invitations, (Correspondence, Includes Speech To New York Sons Of Italy, 6/2000,), Apr 2000; (7 folders) (Box 61)
    - United States Telecom Association, (Itinerary, Correspondence), 20-23 Feb 2000 (Box 61)
    - Victory Luncheon, New York State Conservative Party Invitation Card, (Guest Speakers George W. Bush and Rick Lazio), 14 Jul 2000 (Box 61)
    - J.F.K. School Of Government Health Policy Conference, (Itinerary, Correspondence), 11-13 Jan 2001 (Box 61)
  - Legislation
    - Defense, Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed by R. Lazio, Dec 1992-Oct 1999; (4 folders) (Box 62)
    - Congressional Correspondence (‘Dear Colleague’ Letters) From Rick Lazio RE: Misc. Legislation, Jul 1993-Jan 1997 (Boxes 62, 158)
    - Congressional Record Articles Written By R. Lazio, Feb 1993-Nov 1994; (4 folders) (Box 62)
    - Congressional Reform – Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio, Mar 1993-Mar 1995 (Box 62)
    - Correspondence (misc.) Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio, May 1993-Oct 1999 (Box 62)
    - Finance – Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio, Apr 1993-Mar 1998; (2 folders) (Box 62)
    - High Tech – Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio, Mar 1993-Feb 1997 (Box 62)
    - Labor – Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio, Aug 1993-Aug 1998 (Box 62)
    - NAFTA, (Op-Ed Text, Drafts ‘Why I’ll Vote For NAFTA, By Rick Lazio, Remarks by Jack Kemp, Alan Reynolds, Correspondence, Includes Letter To R. Lazio From Jack Kemp 11/12/1993, Press Clippings, Report – "Response of the Office of the U.S. Trade Representative To The Perot…"), Jun-Nov 1993; (4 folders) (Boxes 62, 63, 158)
    - Trade – Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio, Jun 1993-May 1999 (Box 63)
    - Trade – Co-Sponsorship Letter Signed By R. Lazio, National Institute For World Trade, Jul 1994 (Box 63)
    - Bills Sponsored By R. Lazio, (Bill Language), Jan 1994 – Apr 1997; (4 folders) (Box 63)
    - Crime, (Congressional Correspondence, Background Material), Jun-Aug 1994 (Box 63)
    - Judiciary (misc.) Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio, Mar 1994-Sep 1999; (2 folders) (Box 63)
    - AIDS - AIDS Drug Assistance Program, (Correspondence), (1 of 5), Feb 1997-May 1999 (Box 64)
    - AIDS – Housing Opportunities For Persons With AIDS, (Correspondence), (2 of 5), Mar 1998 - Sep 2000 (Box 64)
    - AIDS – Needle Exchange Programs, (Press Releases, Correspondence, Background Material), (3 of 5), 1995-2000 (Box 64)
    - AIDS – Partner Notification, (Correspondence, Background Material), (4 of 5), Sep 1998 (Box 64)
    - AIDS - Ricky Ray Hemophilia Relief Fund, (Correspondence), (5 of 5), Dec 1995-Apr 1999 (Box 64)
    - Federal Housing Administration, (Correspondence RE: Mortgage Insurance Program, Background Material, Memos, Press Releases, Talking Points, Memos, Press Releases, Talking Points, Bill Language/Draft, Proposal, Ginnie Mae Financial Statements), May 1995-Jul 1996; (8 folders) (Box 65)
    - Low Income Housing Preservation and Resident Home Ownership, (Discussion Drafts, Grant Proposals, Summaries, Correspondence, Congressional Budget Office Report, Talking Points, Testimony Statements To Senate Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, Legal Briefs), Apr 1992-Dec 1996; (13 folders) (Boxes 65, 66, 158)
    - Low Income Housing Tax Credit, (Correspondence, Talking Points, Press Releases), Sep 1997-Mar 1998 (Box 66)
    - Low Income Housing Tax Credit, (Information Packet, Correspondence, Press Clips), Dec 1995; (2 folders) (Box 66)
    - National Home ownership Strategy, (Correspondence, Report), May-Jun 1995 (Box 67)
    - Title 1 Home Improvement Loan Program, (Correspondence, Talking Points, (Background Material, Fed. Housing Admin. Report, Press Releases), Jun 1995-May 1997; (2 folders) (Box 67)
    - Community Services Block Grant, (Correspondence, Talking Points, Memoranda), 1996-1997; (4 folders) (Box 67)
    - Pro-Life/Abortion, (Overview of Legislation), Jan 1996 (Box 67)
    - Real Estate Settlement Procedures Act, (Congressional Staff Briefing, Background Information, Press Clippings), Dec 1995-Sep 1996; (2 folders) (Box 67)
    - Aid to India, (U.S. A.I.D. Congressional Report, FY 1998, Letter From Pres. Bill Clinton), 11 Sep 1998 (Box 67)
    - Correspondence, Congressional – Legislative/Appropriations, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), Jan-Dec 1997; (3 folders) (Boxes 67, 68)
    - Cost of Living Adjustments, Resolution 13, (Background Material), Apr 1997 (Box 68)
    - Dept. of Defense Breast Cancer Research Program, (Correspondence From R. Lazio), May 1997-Sep 1998 (Box 68)
    - Foreign Operations Appropriations Bill, (Congressional Correspondence), Nov 1997 (Box 68)
    - Greek American Lobbying Org. (AHEPA), (Breakdown of Lazio Voting Record, Correspondence, AHEPA "Score Card" Reports), Jun 1997-Jun 1998 (Box 68)
    - H.R. 1 Working Families Flexibility Act, (Memoranda, Correspondence), Mar 1997 (Box 68)
    - H.R.2 The Housing and Responsibility Act of 1997, (Article By R. Lazio, The American Sound) (Box 68)
    - H.R.2 The Housing and Responsibility Act of 1997, (Correspondence, press clippings, press release, background material, Speech drafts, Lazio statements), Apr-May 1997; (2 folders) (Box 68)
    - H.R.2 The Housing and Responsibility Act, (Lazio Floor Statement, Notes, Correspondence), Apr 1997-Aug 1998 (Box 68)
    - H.R. 10 Financial Services Competition Act, (Correspondence, Notes, Lazio statement, Press Clippings, Talking Points, Lazio Thrift Amendment), Jun-Mar 1998; (7 folders) (Boxes 68-69, 158)
    - H.R. 589 Fair Housing Act – ‘Sober Homes’, (Correspondence From R. Lazio, Memoranda, Background Material, Congressional Research Service Report, Anti-Drug Abuse Act), Feb-Jul 1997; (2 folders) (Box 69)
    - H.R. 1709, Medicare, Food Stamps, WIC Privatization, (Correspondence), May-Oct 1997; (2 folders) (Box 69)
    - H.R. 2441 Correspondence Regarding 31(a) Fees, (Background Material for H.R. 2441), 1997-1998 (Box 69)
    - Health Care, (Thank You Letters From Special Interest Groups To R. Lazio), Feb 1997 - May 2000 (Box 69)
    - International Family Planning, (Correspondence, Including Copies of White House Correspondence), Jan-Feb 1997 (Box 69)
    - Job Corps Support, (Congressional Correspondence), Apr-May 1997 (Box 69)
    - Labor, Lazio Letter Drafts, (with Notes), (Letter Carriers Breakfast Talking Points), May-Nov 1997; (2 folders) (Box 69)
    - Labor/Letter Carriers and Seafarer’s Union, (Outline of Carrier and Seafarer Concerns), Aug 1997-Sep 1998 (Box 69)
    - Letters Signed By R. Lazio Supporting Misc. Legislation, Jul-Dec 1997 (Box 69)
    - Mexican Trucking Restrictions, (Congressional Correspondence), Mar 1997-Jul 1999 (Box 69)
    - Middle East/Israel Congressional Correspondence and Memoranda, (Includes Two Letters From Pres. Bill Clinton), Dec 1997-Apr 1998 (Box 70)
    - National Association of Letter Carriers, (Speech (9/17/1995), Correspondence, Press Clippings), Apr-Aug 1997 (Box 70)
    - Quality Childcare Loan Forgiveness Act, (Press Clippings, Background Material, Speech Text), Jun 1997-May 1998 (Box 70)
    - Railroad Retirement Act, (Correspondence, Bill Language), May 1997 (Box 70)
    - Real Estate Settlement Procedures Act, (Background Material, Talking Points, Notes), Feb-Mar 1997; (2 folders) (Box 70)
    - Russia Arms Sales To Iran, (Memoranda, Correspondence), Sep 1997 (Box 70)
    - Subcommittee on Housing and Community Opportunity, (Briefing Book), 7 Jan 1997; (2 folders) (Box 70)
    - Thank You Letters From Special Interest Groups and Congressional Members For Legislative Support, Sep 1997-Feb 1999; (2 folders) (Box 70)
    - Ambro, Jerome – Post Office Naming, (Correspondence, Bill Language), Feb 1998 (Box 70)
    - American Society of Radiologic Technologists, (Correspondence, Periodical Featuring Column on R. Lazio), Apr-Nov 1998 (Box 70)
    - American Society of Radiologic Technologists, (Medicaid Waiver Briefing, Background Material), Mar-Jul 1998 (Box 71)
    - American Society of Radiologic Technologists, (Report: Minimizing Risk, Maximizing Quality, 1998 (Box 71)
    - Bills/Appropriations Presented To R. Lazio For Approval RE: Labor, Jul 1998-Apr 2000 (Box 71)
    - Bills/Appropriations Presented To R. Lazio For Approval RE: Environment, Feb 1998 (Box 71)
    - Bills/Appropriations Presented To R. Lazio For Approval RE: Labor, Mar 1998 - May 2000 (Box 71)
    - Bill Language, H.R. 5193, 5267, 5274, 4796, 4920, 1998 (Box 71)
    - Bills/Appropriations Presented and Approved By R. Lazio, Oct 1998-Dec 1999 (Box 71)
    - Child Care and Development Block Grant, (Correspondence), Apr 1998 (Box 71)
    - Community Services Block Grant, (Correspondence, Background Material), Jul 1997-Oct 1998 (Box 71)
    - Congressional Gold Medal – Nelson Mandela, (Memoranda/Correspondence), Feb 1998 (Box 71)
    - Correspondence, Congressional – (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio – Transportation, Education, Defense, Technology), Jul 1998-Oct 2000 (Box 71)
    - Correspondence, Congressional – Legislative/Appropriations, (Co-Sponsorship Letters Signed By R. Lazio), Jan-Nov 1998 (Box 71)
    - Correspondence Form Letters (Drafts) From R. Lazio RE: Misc. Legislation/Legislative Issues, 1998 (Box 71)
    - Crime, (Co-Sponsored Crime-Related Legislation, Correspondence, Memoranda), Jun-Sep 1998 (Box 71)
    - Environmental Issues, (Long Island Sound Restoration; Drinking Water; Lazio Testimony on Water Resources), Jul-Nov 1999 (Box 71)
    - F.D.A. Modernization Act, (Plans For Implementing Clinical Trials Database, Notes), 1998; (2 folders) (Boxes 71, 158)
    - H.R. 219 Home Owners Insurance Availability Act, (Press Releases, Correspondence, Background Material), Jun-Jul 1998 (Box 72)
    - H.R. 856 Puerto Rico Self Determination Act, (Speech (3/4/1998), Correspondence) (Box 72)
    - H.R. 2090, Wartime Violation of Italian American Civil Liberties Act, (Correspondence, Press Release, Bill Language), Jan 1997-Oct 1998 (Box 72)
    - H.R. 2281 Digital Millennium Copyright Act, (World Intellectual Property Organization Correspondence, Memoranda, Notes,, Lazio Statement, Speech Drafts, Briefing Materials), Jun-Sep 1998; (5 folders) (Box 72)
    - H.R. 3206 Fair Housing Amendments, (Letter Drafts From R. Lazio, Bill Summaries, Correspondence), Feb-Apr 1998 (Box 72)
    - H.R. 3779 Breast and Cervical Cancer Treatment Act, (Bill Summary, Correspondence), May-Jul 1998 (Box 72)
    - H.R. 3899 American Homeownership Act (Mark-up), (Lazio Statements, Press Releases, Correspondence, Background Material), Jul-Oct 1998 (Box 72)
    - H.R. 4005, 1756 Hearing On Money Laundering, (Lazio Statement), 11 Jun 1998 (Box 72)
    - Healthcare, NY, (Summary of Lazio Voting Record, Correspondence), Apr 1998 Oct 2000 (Box 72)
    - Hispanic Voting Record, (Lazio Accomplishments, Memo), Oct 1998 (Box 72)
    - Iron Workers Breakfast, (Discussion Points), Jun 1999 (Box 72)
    - Italian American Issues – Italian American Heritage Month, (Correspondence, Bill Language), Oct 1999 (Box 72)
    - Job Corps – Funding, (Talking Points, Action Plan, Correspondence, Handwritten Notes), Sep 1997-Jul 1998; (3 folders) (Boxes 73, 158)
    - Legislative Research Presented To Rick Lazio By Staff (Misc. Issues), Mar 1998-Jan 1999; (2 folders) (Box 73)
    - Letters Signed By R. Lazio Supporting Misc. Legislation, Feb-Oct 1998 (Box 73)
    - National Oil Heat Research Alliance Act, (Correspondence, Bill Language), Dec 1998-Jan 1999 (Box 73)
    - Quality Childcare Loan Forgiveness Act, (Bill Text, Amendment Text, Press Releases, Notes, Correspondence, Background Material), Apr-Oct 1998; (5 folders) (Box 73)
    - Quality Housing and Work Responsibility Act, (Lazio Floor Statements, Press Releases, Background Material), May-Oct 1998; (3 folders) (Boxes 73, 158)
    - Real Estate Settlement Procedures Act and Truth In Lending Act, (Lazio Statement, Correspondence), Jul-Aug 1998 (Box 74)
    - Section 415 Pension Provisions, (Memoranda, Correspondence), Jul-Aug 1998 (Box 74)
    - Steel Industry, (Correspondence), Jul-Oct 1998 (Box 74)
    - AFL-CIO, (Memoranda, Talking Points For AFL-CIO Breakfast (7/15/99), Correspondence), Mar-Oct 1999 (Box 74)
    - Alitalia Labor Dispute, (Correspondence, Copy of Congressional Letter To Pres. Bill Clinton), 12 Apr 1999 (Box 74)
    - Alternative Certification and Licensure of Teachers Act, (Bill Language, Correspondence), 1999 (Box 74)
    - Anti-Environmental Rider Opposition, (Press Releases, Correspondence, Talking Points), 11/1999 (Box 74)
    - Armed Forces Of National Liberation, (Correspondence, Background Information), Sep 1999 (Box 74)
    - Art Loss Register/New York Arts Bill, (Correspondence, Background Material), Dec 1998-Jan 1999 (Box 74)
    - Bills Presented To/Approved By R. Lazio, Jan-Dec 1999; (8 folders) (Box 74)
    - Campaign Finance Reform…Shays-Meehan Bill, (Correspondence, Background Material, Congressional Research Service Report), Feb 1998-Sep 1999 (Box 75)
    - China Relations, Normal Trade Relations, (Correspondence, Notes, Press Clippings, Background Information…Includes Letter From Pres. Bill Clinton, 8/4/1999) (Box 75)
    - China, World Trade Association, (Correspondence, Background Information), Jun-Aug 1999 (Box 75)
    - Correspondence, (Congressional/White House Correspondence, RE: Defense, Veterans—Legislative Issues, Programs, Funding), Mar-Oct 1999; (2 folders) (Box 75)
    - East Timor, (Correspondence, Background Information), Apr-May 1999 (Box 75)
    - Education Flex Partnership Act, (Background Information, Bill Language), 1999 (Box 75)
    - Egypt, Religious Persecution, (Background Information, Correspondence…Includes Letter From Pres. Bill Clinton, 7/21/1999) (Box 75)
    - English Immersion Bill, (Correspondence, Notes, Background Information, Bill Language), Jan-Apr 1999; (2 folders) (Box 75)
    - Guadalupe – Hidalgo Land Claims Act, (Background Information), Sep 1999 (Box 75)
    - Health Care, (Health Care Financing Administration General Correspondence), Aug-Nov 2000 (Box 75)
    - H.R. 94 Volunteer Fire Fighter and Rescue Squad Workers Protection Act, (Correspondence and Background Material), May-Aug 1999 (Box 75)
    - H.R. 352, Retirement Savings, (Correspondence, Bill Language), Sep 1999 (Box 75)
    - H.R. 701 Conservation and Reinvestment Act, (Summary and Background Material, Correspondence), Feb-Aug 1999; (2 folders) (Box 76)
    - H.R. 853 Comprehensive Budget Process Reform Act, (Correspondence, Notes, Summary of Bill), May-Jun 1999 (Box 76)
    - H.R. 887,1089, 1954 Philanthropic Contributions, Mutual Fund Disclosure, Rental Fairness, (Background Materials, Floor Statement By R. Lazio), Oct 1999-Mar 2000 (Box 76)
    - H.R. 1070 Breast and Cervical Cancer Treatment Act, (Press Conference Talking Points, Statement To House of Representatives, Bill Summary, Correspondence, Bill Language, Press Releases), Mar 1999 - Feb 2000; (5 folders) (Box 76)
    - H.R. 1095 Debt Relief For Poverty Reduction Act, (Background Information, Notes, Correspondence, Report, Initiatives For Most Heavily Indebted Poor Countries), Sep-Nov 1999; (2 folders) (Box 76)
    - H.R. 1102, Employee Retirement Income Security Act, (Bill Language), 1999 (Box 76)
    - H.R. 1180 The Work Incentives Improvement Act, (Draft of Bill Language, Correspondence, Meeting Notes, Lazio’s Statement (2/8/99), Senate Hearing Text, Notes, Testimonies, Letters of Support, House Republican Conference Floor Prep, Background Info, Budget Office/Cost Estimates), Aug 1988-Apr 1999; (6 folders) (Boxes 76, 77)
    - H.R. 1180 The Work Incentives Improvement Act, (Bill Language), Mar 1999; (5 folders) (Box 77)
    - H.R. 1180 Work Incentives Improvement Act, (Press Releases, Lazio Talking Points, Statement (including drafts), Staff Correspondence), Mar-Jun 1999; (2 folders) (Box 77)
    - H.R. 1180 The Work Incentives Improvement Act, (Hearing Information, Lazio Testimony, General Info, Subcommittee Mark-Up, Summary, Background, Talking Points, Additional Testimonies), Mar-Apr 1999; (3 folders) (Box 77)
    - H.R. 1180 The Work Incentives Improvement Act, (Lazio Floor Statements, Press Clippings, Press Releases), May-Dec 1999; (3 folders) (Box 78)
    - H.R. 1180 The Work Incentives Improvement Act, (Talking Points, Lazio Statement, Colloquy Script Bill Language), May 1999; (2 folders) (Box 78)
    - H.R. 1355 U.N. Arrears Payment Act, (Background Material, Correspondence), Apr-May 1999 (Box 78)
    - H.R. 1660 Public School Modernization Act, (Correspondence, Bill Language), May 1999-Jun 2000 (Box 78)
    - H.R. 1915 Jennifer’s Law, (Floor Statement Drafts, Press Releases, Bill Language, Correspondence, Background Material), Mar 1999 – Mar 2000; (2 folders) (Box 78)
    - H.R. 1995 Teacher Empowerment Act, (Lazio Statement, Speech, Press Release Draft, Correspondence, Bill Language), 1999 (Box 78)
    - H.R. 2401 Holocaust Assets Comm. Extension Act, (Statements by R. Lazio, Press Release, Background Material), Jun 1999 - Feb 2000 (Box 79)
    - H.R. 2434 Worker Paycheck Fairness Act, (Correspondence), Sep 1999 (Box 79)
    - H.R. 2441 Fairness In Securities Transactions Act of 1999, (Notes, Background Material, Senate Hearing, Testimonies, (Lazio Correspondence to Commerce Committee, Lazio Statements, Hearing Notes, Proposed Questions), Jul 1998 - Oct 1999; (13 folders) (Box 79)
    - H.R. 2442 Wartime Violation of Italian American…,(Lazio Testimony, Notes, Bill Language, Press Clippings, Background Material), Jan 1999 Jan 2000; (5 folders) (Box 79)
    - H.R. 2488, Tax For Lending of Finance Companies, (Correspondence), May-Oct 1999; (2 folders) (Box 80)
    - H.R. 2520 Credit For Voluntary Actions Act, (Lazio Talking Points, Statements, Press Releases, Correspondence and Background Material), May-Sep 1999; (2 folders) (Box 80)
    - H.R. 2684 VA/HUD and Independent Agencies Appropriations Act, (Lazio Floor Statement, Correspondence, Feature Article On Cover of ‘Modern Homes’ "Meet Rick Lazio"), Jul-Aug 1999 (Box 80)
    - H.R. 2684 Veteran’s Medical Care/V.A.-H.U.D., (Colloquy Text, Correspondence, Background Material), Sep 1999 (Box 80)
    - H.R. 2735, Repeal of Occupational Taxes, (Bill Language), 1999 (Box 80)
    - H.R. 2829, Minimum Wage State Flexibility Act, (Bill Language, Correspondence, Background Info), Sep 1999 (Box 80)
    - H.R. 3064 D.C. Appropriations Act, (Conference Report), Oct 1999; (3 folders) (Box 80)
    - H.R. 3081, Wage and Employment Growth Act, (Bill Language, Press Releases, Talking Points, Statement by R. Lazio, Correspondence, Closing Floor Statement, Minimum Wage Provisions Report, Talking Points), Mar-Nov 1999; (9 folders) (Boxes 80, 81)
    - H.R. 3441 National Environmental Education Act, (Report, Key Accomplishments of Act, Correspondence), Oct 1999 (Box 81)
    - Health Care Related Legislative Research Presented To R. Lazio By Staff (Misc. Issues), Jan-Jul 1999; (2 folders) (Box 81)
    - Housing Issues (Misc.), (Includes R. Lazio Floor Statement RE Homeowner Insurance), 28 Apr 1999 (Box 81)
    - Incarceration Of NYC Journalist, Lori Berenson In Peru, (Correspondence), Mar-May 1999 (Box 81)
    - Independent Contractors, Minimum Wage Tax Bill, (Correspondence, Teamsters), Sep-Oct 1999 (Box 81)
    - India, Foreign Assistance, (Talking Points, Background Information), Jul 1999 (Box 81)
    - Israel – Jerusalem, Capital City/Anti-Semitism In Russia, (Congressional Correspondence), Mar-Aug 1999 (Box 81)
    - Joint Committee on Taxation Estimated Budget Effects, H.R. 2488, 3081, 1999 (Box 81)
    - Lazio Voting Record For 1999, Dec 1999 (Box 81)
    - Legislation (misc.) Considered By R. Lazio For Sponsorship, (Correspondence Background Material), Apr-Aug 1999 (Box 81)
    - Letters Signed By R. Lazio Supporting Misc. Legislation, Jan-Feb 1999 (Box 81)
    - Low Income Home Energy Assistance Program, (Press Clippings, Background Material), Feb-Jul 1999 (Box 81)
    - Medical Device Reprocessing, (Background Material, Memoranda) (Box 82)
    - Microenterprise Programs/Loans, (Correspondence), Jun 1999 (Box 82)
    - Middle East – WYE River Agreement, (Congressional Correspondence), Mar 1999 (Box 82)
    - Minimum Wage Bill, (Press Clippings), Sep-Oct 1999 (Box 82)
    - Minimum Wage Increase, (Correspondence, Staff, Congressional, Special Interest, (Notes, Research and Background Materials, Legislative Proposal, Bill Language Draft), Jan 1998-Jul 1999; (5 folders) (Box 82)
    - Mountain Top Mining, (Lazio Statement For Press Conference, Talking Points, Draft Letter To Pres Clinton, Correspondence, Press Clippings), Nov 1999-Apr 2000 (Box 82)
    - NATO Expansion, (Correspondence, Background Information), Mar-Jun 1999 (Box 82)
    - Pan Am Flight 103 Witness To Justice Act, (Correspondence), Apr 1999 (Box 82)
    - Russian Money Laundering Hearing, (Statement By R. Lazio To House Com. Banking and Financial Services), Sep 1999 (Box 82)
    - S. 1059 National Defense Authorization Act, (Summary of Provisions, Letters of Support), 1999 (Box 82)
    - School of The Americas, (Background Information, Correspondence), Feb-Sep 1999 (Box 82)
    - School Prayer, (Research, Notes, Background Material), Jun-Jul 1999 (Box 82)
    - Sheet Metal and Air Conditioning Contractor’s National Association Luncheon, (Discussion Points), Jul-Aug 1999 (Box 82)
    - Section 8 Opt-outs Hearing, (Lazio Statement, Background Material), 1999 (Box 82)
    - Special Requests (misc.), (Requests Made/Correspondence To R. Lazio), Jan-Dec 1999 (Box 82)
    - Taiwan Security Enhancement Act, (Background Information, Correspondence), Aug-Oct 1999 (Box 82)
    - Tax Exempt Associations, (Correspondence), Feb 1999 (Box 82)
    - Tax-Related Legislation (Misc.), Considered By R. Lazio For Sponsorship, (Correspondence, Background Material), Jun-Aug 1999 (Box 83)
    - Tax Relief For Working Americans Act, (Bill Highlights, Correspondence), May 1999 (Box 83)
    - Transportation Equity Act, (Colloquy Text), Jun 1999 (Box 83)
    - Travel, Spousal Business Travel Tax Deduction, (Background Information), 1999 (Box 83)
    - Treasury Exchange Stabilization Fund, (Correspondence, Background Information, Notes), Jul 1999 (Box 83)
    - U.N. Development Program, (Background Information, Correspondence), May-Jul 1999 (Box 83)
    - U.S. Customs Service Authorization, (Background Information, Correspondence), Sep-Oct 1999 (Box 83)
    - Voluntary Action - Greenhouse Gas Emissions – (Bill Summary, Report, Bill Language, Co-Sponsorship Letter Signed By Rick Lazio), Apr-Jul 1999; (3 folders) (Boxes 83, 158)